cannabis.info 2019-07-02

# Privacy policy - Cannabis.info

This page with our Privacy Policy is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information if anyone decided to visit our website.

If you choose to visit this website, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The personal information that we collect are used for providing and improving the user experience on this website.

We want to inform you that whenever you visit this website, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called 'Log Data'. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of this website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

We also make use of so-called "cookies". Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used as an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Our website uses these cookies to collection information and to improve our service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies in your browser. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some parts of this website.

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on December 8, 2017.

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us by using our contact form.
